{
    "data": {
        "title": "JavaScript Flashcards",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "What language are Express apps written in?",
                "hint": "It starts with a \"J\"",
                "answer": "JavaScript"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is one way a website can store data in a user's browser?",
                "hint": "They are delicious with milk",
                "answer": "Cookies"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is a common way to shorten the response object's name inside middleware?",
                "hint": "It has the same abbreviation as \"resolution\"",
                "answer": "res"
            },
            {
                "question": "How many different values can booleans have?",
                "hint": "Think: binary",
                "answer": "2"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which HTML element can contain JavaScript?",
                "hint": "It starts with an \"s\"",
                "answer": "<script>"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is bravado?",
                "hint": "brave",
                "answer": "a swaggering show of courage"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is cacophony?",
                "hint": "noisy",
                "answer": "loud confusing disagreeable sounds"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is capricious?",
                "hint": "idk",
                "answer": "determined by chance or impulse rather than by necessity"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is carte blanche?",
                "hint": "idk",
                "answer": "complete freedom or authority to act"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is deja vu?",
                "hint": "french",
                "answer": "the experience of thinking a new situation already occurred"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is zealous?",
                "hint": "idk",
                "answer": "marked by active interest and enthusiasm"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is white elephant?",
                "hint": "idk",
                "answer": "a valuable possession whose upkeep is excessively expensive"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is waft?",
                "hint": "flag",
                "answer": "a long flag; often tapering"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is vile?",
                "hint": "idk",
                "answer": "morally reprehensible"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is vicarious?",
                "hint": "idk",
                "answer": "experienced at secondhand"
            }
        ]
    }
}